Finding Aid for the Edward Huntsman-Trout Papers LSC.1186
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Client
  - Client: Uplifters Club, Los Angeles., Ranch flower show., March-April 1941; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Client: Upper Manatee River., Photograph., December 25, 1924; 1 item. (Box 38, Folder 53)
  - Client: Vanderlip., Estate., March 1929; 1 item. (Box 138)
  - Client: Villa d'Este. Photograph., 1 item. (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Client: Visel., Residence., February-May 1951; 6 items. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Client: Von Bibra., Residence., February-October 1939; 7 items. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Client: Von Binzer. (Box 126)
  - Client: Wagenseller., Garden., August 1941; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Client: Weaver., Residence., May-November 1956; 4 items. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Client: Weaver., 2 items. (Box 48)
  - Client: Weaver, Jr., Grounds., May 1971-January 1972; 8 items. (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Client: Weaver, Jr., Correspondence, accounts., April 1971-May 1972; 37 items. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Client: Weaver, Jr., Plans., 1971; 9 items. (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Client: Weaver, Jr., Correspondence, invoices, etc., April 1971-April 1972, n.d.; 65 items. (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Client: Weaver, Jr. [and other clients]. Engineering specs. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Client: Webb School of California. (Box 110)
  - Client: Webb School of California. Dorms. (Box 115)
  - Client: Webb School of California. Chandler Field. (Box 116)
  - Client: Webb School of California. Pool and tennis court. (Box 117)
  - Client: Webb School of California, Claremont., 1 item. (Box 136)
  - Client: Webb School of California, Claremont., March 1960-April 1966.; 12 items. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Client: Webb School of California, Claremont. Printed brochure. (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Client: Webb School of California, Claremont., 1 item. (Box 71)
  - Client: Weiner., Grounds., January-December 1956; 6 items. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Client: Weiner., Additions., April-July 1966; 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Client: Weingarden., Residence., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Client: Weisel., Residence., March 1953; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Client: Wells. (Box 108)
  - Client: West Coast Bond and Mortgage Company., November 1931.; 1 item. (Box 138)
  - Client: Western Mortgage Company, Los Angeles., October 1948.; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Client: Whitney., Additions., January 1966-August 1967; 11 item. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Client: Whittier., Garden., March 1951; 2 items. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Client: Whittier College, Whittier., August-September 1948.; 4 items. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Client: Whittier College, Whittier., September 1948-July 1949.; 3 items. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Client: Whittier College, Whittier., Wanberg Dormitory., September 1949; 1 item. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Client: Whittlesey., Grounds., October-November 1952; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Client: Wing., Residence., September 1956; 3 items. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Client: Winnett., Estate., September 1928-March 1929; 21 item. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Client: Winnett, P.G. Photographs - Mott Studios., 7 items. (Box 133)
  - Client: Winnett, P.G. Photographs - W.M. Clarke., 10 items. (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Client: Winnett, P.G. Drawing of wall - Mott photograph. (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Client: Winnett, P.G. Mott studios envelope (ephemera)., 1 item. (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Client: Winnett, P.G. Drawing on board (damaged - in 3 pieces). (Box 132)
  - Client: Winnett.P.G. Photographs - W.M. Clarke., 7 items. (Box 132)
  - Client: Wolf. Photographs., 11 item. (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Client: Wolff, Jr., Grounds., April-May 1962; 3 items. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Client: Wolff, Jr., Grounds development., August 1970; 1 item. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Client: Wolff, Jr., Correspondence, accounts., December 1965-May 1971; 56 items. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Client: Wood, E., Cottage., July 1923; 9 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: Wood, E.G. Cottage, Carmel. (Box 91)
  - Client: Wood, J., Residence., June-November 1951; 3 items. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Client: Woodbury., Garden., July 1966; 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Client: Woods, E.R. Mounted photograph., 1 item. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Client: Wygant., Garden., February 1937; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Client: Wykoff., Garden., May 1946; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Client: Wyle., Residence., September 1955-February 1956; 5 items. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Client: Wyle Laboratories, El Segundo., 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Client: Wynns., Residence., September 1948; 2 items. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Client: Young., Cottage (photographs)., n.d.; 7 items. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Client: Young., Cottage., March 1929-October 1935; 7 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: Young., Cottage., March 1929-October 1935; 4 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: Younkin., Residence., March-April 1950; 3 items. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Client: Zeiler., Alterations., December 1965-May 1967; 4 items. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Client: Zimmerla., Residence., December 1949-December 1950; 4 items. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Client: Zuckerman., Residence., September 1951-August 1952; 10 items. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Client: Zurich Insurance Company, Los Angeles., December 1955.; 4 items. (Box 17, Folder 5)